<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docs on FocusTabs</title>
    <link>https://focus-tabs.com/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docs on FocusTabs</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Website built by Guilherme Feitosa.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://focus-tabs.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Can I Use FocusTabs?</title>
      <link>https://focus-tabs.com/page/how-can-i-use-focustabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://focus-tabs.com/page/how-can-i-use-focustabs/</guid>
      <description>How Can I Use FocusTabs? By following the steps below, you will not get lost in a sea of tabs anymore. From now on, you will always find your flow.&#xA;Installation Install From Release Download the latest release from the Releases Unzip the downloaded ZIP file Open Chrome and navigate to chrome://extensions Enable &amp;ldquo;Developer mode&amp;rdquo; Drag and drop the unzipped folder into the extensions page Install From Source Clone the repository:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Was The Process of Building the Extension?</title>
      <link>https://focus-tabs.com/page/how-did-you-build-the-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://focus-tabs.com/page/how-did-you-build-the-extension/</guid>
      <description>How Did You Build the Extension? Developing FocusTabs has been an enlightening journey filled with challenges, decisions, and ultimately, valuable lessons. In this post-mortem analysis, we&amp;rsquo;ll delve into the process, decisions made, mistakes encountered, and most importantly, the lessons learned throughout the development of the project.&#xA;Decisions and Mistakes 1. Underestimating API Integration Complexity One of our early mistakes was underestimating the complexity of integrating multiple APIs, especially the OpenAI API for automated tab grouping suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Your Mission Statement?</title>
      <link>https://focus-tabs.com/page/what-is-your-mission-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://focus-tabs.com/page/what-is-your-mission-statement/</guid>
      <description>What is Your Mission Statement? When you are working online, especially when trying to multitask, it is extremely easy to get lost in a sea of 30-40 tabs that leads you floundering. Indeed, cluttered tabs not only reduce your productivity but can also leave you more stressed and frustrated, as you struggle to keep track of everything. FocusTabs was built to address this issue, assisting the user with keeping track of all of the tabs needed to achieve each of their goals, and hence improving their overall virtual experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Built the Extension?</title>
      <link>https://focus-tabs.com/page/who-built-the-extension/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://focus-tabs.com/page/who-built-the-extension/</guid>
      <description>Who Built the Extension? FocusTabs was built as part of the curriculum for University of Pennsylvania&amp;rsquo;s CIS3500 class (&amp;ldquo;Software Design &amp;amp; Engineering&amp;rdquo;), instructed by Professor Jérémie O. Lumbroso, during the 2024 spring semester.&#xA;Team FocusTabs was built by Anirudh Bharadwaj, Eshan Singhal, Guilherme Feitosa, and Kofi Addae-Sakyi – all undergraduate students at the University of Pennsylvania.&#xA;Acknowledgements We would like to thank Professor Jérémie O. Lumbroso for his fundamental mentorship all throughout the development of FocusTabs.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
